# Paidamoyo - Janet Azehko

E-Mail Me! LinkedIn GitHub

I am a former circus performer, current fashion design student and self taught web developer seeking a career in tech that suits my professional skills, ability to quickly learn new things, and my love of finding creative ways to look at the world. My decade-long career as an artist and performer gives me the unique ability to find creative and empathetic solutions to every problem. I can bring creativity, drive, and passion to your organization.

#### **Education**

## City College of San Francisco

Associates of Art Fashion Design (December 2021)

## **Academy of Art University**

**Bachelors of Art** Fashion Product Development (TBD)

#### Skills

## Web Development:

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React

Tools: Visual Studio, Git, GitHub, Chrome Developer Tools, NPM, Boostrap,

LESS, Node.js

## **Project Management:**

Scheduling

**Event Production** 

Budgeting

Conflict Management

## Fashion Design:

Patternmaking

Sewing

Illustration

#### Experience

#### Grabango

Quality Trainer 1/2019 - 10/2019

- Helped teams collect, clean and label data and images.
- Identified and categorized objects in images and videos.
- Annotated actions in images and videos.

Used various sets of rules to process data sets, logged exceptions as they
occurred.

#### **Tech Inclusion**

Social Media Volunteer 1/2018 - 10/2019

- Plan and execute social media campaigns for events in New York San Francisco, London, Melbourne and others both nationally and internationally.
- Successfully implemented a new video interview component to Social Media that increased follower engagement.
- Managed social media accounts with over 3,000 followers.

### **Kinetic Arts Center**

Administrative Assistant 6/2018 - 3/2019

- Managed front desk, including telephones, mail/messages, faxes and visitors.
- Reviewed adnd entered class enrollment into MindBody software system.
- Registered new clients and assist with purchases of class packages and merchandise.
- Provided corespondence for customer concerns in person, by phone and email.
- Managed community donations on behalf of Kinetic Arts.

## **Project Erostribe**

Creative Director 1/2010-Current

- Supervised project collaborations with internationally recognized recording artists such as Shpongle and Ott, World Bodypaint Champions such as Trina Merry and Matteo Arfanotti and companies such as Google and Microsoft.
- Directed art projects for events such as Re: Creation San Francisco, Burning Man 2017, Hot Couture
- Raised over \$40,000 in private funds.
- Managed social media accounts totaling 20K in followers.

